[
  {
    "question": "オーグメンチン",
    "correct": "アモキシシリンクラブランカリウム",
    "choices": [
      "コハクソリフェナシン",
      "エチゾラム",
      "アモキシシリンクラブランカリウム",
      "トラマドール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ミグシス",
    "correct": "ロメリジン",
    "choices": [
      "ロメリジン",
      "チモロール",
      "シベンゾリンコハク",
      "エパルレスタット"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ノバミン",
    "correct": "プロクロルペラジンマレイン",
    "choices": [
      "クアゼパム",
      "モンテルカスト",
      "ピリドキシン",
      "プロクロルペラジンマレイン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "レスタミンコーワ",
    "correct": "ジフェンヒドラミン",
    "choices": [
      "ブデソニド・ホルモテロール",
      "ケトプロフェン",
      "ミルナシプラン",
      "ジフェンヒドラミン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "フロリード",
    "correct": "ミコナゾール",
    "choices": [
      "ミコナゾール",
      "ボリコナゾール",
      "イトラコナゾール",
      "フルコナゾール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "セタプリル",
    "correct": "アラセプリル",
    "choices": [
      "クロルマジノン",
      "トコフェロールニコチンエステル",
      "タクロリムス",
      "アラセプリル"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ストロカイン",
    "correct": "オキセサゼイン",
    "choices": [
      "テルミサルタン・ヒドロクロロチアジド",
      "フェノフィブラート",
      "ベタメタゾンエステル",
      "オキセサゼイン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "アタラックス",
    "correct": "ヒドロキシジンパモ",
    "choices": [
      "ヒドロキシジンパモ",
      "テガフール・ギメラシル・オテラシル",
      "アスパラギンカルシウム",
      "オキシコドン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ロイケリン",
    "correct": "メルカプトプリン",
    "choices": [
      "ニトラゼパム",
      "メルカプトプリン",
      "レバミピド",
      "バルサルタン・アムロジピンベシル"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "マイスタン",
    "correct": "クロバザム",
    "choices": [
      "アモキシシリン",
      "リスペリドン",
      "ブホルミン",
      "クロバザム"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "メンドン",
    "correct": "クロラゼプカリウム",
    "choices": [
      "ジエノゲスト",
      "タカルシトール",
      "クロラゼプカリウム",
      "トラピジル"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "テトラミド",
    "correct": "ミアンセリン",
    "choices": [
      "ピリドキサールリンエステル",
      "フルチカゾンプロピオンエステル",
      "ブロナンセリン",
      "ミアンセリン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ビブラマイシン",
    "correct": "ドキシサイクリン",
    "choices": [
      "ドキシサイクリン",
      "ジソピラミド",
      "ミノサイクリン",
      "アンブリセンタン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ハリゾン",
    "correct": "アムホテリシン",
    "choices": [
      "クリンダマイシンリンエステル",
      "ヘパリン",
      "アムホテリシン",
      "トラゾドン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "リボトリール",
    "correct": "クロナゼパム",
    "choices": [
      "エピナスチン",
      "オメプラゾール",
      "クロナゼパム",
      "リファンピシン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ベプリコール",
    "correct": "ベプリジル",
    "choices": [
      "ベプリジル",
      "ポリスチレンスルホン",
      "テルビナフィン",
      "アクタリット"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "デュファストン",
    "correct": "ジドロゲステロン",
    "choices": [
      "ノルエチステロン・エチニルエストラジオール",
      "ジドロゲステロン",
      "アムロジピンベシル",
      "メドロキシプロゲステロン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ジスロマック",
    "correct": "アジスロマイシン",
    "choices": [
      "クラリスロマイシン",
      "アジスロマイシン",
      "ロキシスロマイシン",
      "エリスロマイシン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "デカドロン",
    "correct": "デキサメタゾン",
    "choices": [
      "カプトプリル",
      "デキサメタゾン",
      "ベタメタゾン",
      "ピレンゼピン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "コレミナール",
    "correct": "フルタゾラム",
    "choices": [
      "クレンブテロール",
      "フルタゾラム",
      "エスタゾラム",
      "エペリゾン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "アリメジン",
    "correct": "アリメマジン",
    "choices": [
      "アリメマジン",
      "ランタン",
      "アズレンスルホン・グルタミン",
      "イトラコナゾール"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "オプソ",
    "correct": "モルヒネ",
    "choices": [
      "テモカプリル",
      "メキシレチン",
      "チニダゾール",
      "モルヒネ"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "プロバンサイン",
    "correct": "プロパンテリン",
    "choices": [
      "ジサイクロミン・アルミニウム",
      "デキサメタゾン",
      "クロルフェネシンカルバミンエステル",
      "プロパンテリン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ロイコン",
    "correct": "アデニン",
    "choices": [
      "イトラコナゾール",
      "アジルサルタン・アムロジピンベシル",
      "サルブタモール",
      "アデニン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ピレチア",
    "correct": "プロメタジン",
    "choices": [
      "プロメタジン",
      "フラビンアデニンジヌクレオチド",
      "ベルベリン・ゲンノショウコエキス",
      "ボセンタン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "メチルエルゴメトリン",
    "correct": "メチルエルゴメトリンマレイン",
    "choices": [
      "グリメピリド",
      "アジルサルタン・アムロジピンベシル",
      "メチルエルゴメトリンマレイン",
      "フルバスタチン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "アスパラカリウム",
    "correct": "アスパラギンカリウム",
    "choices": [
      "ラマトロバン",
      "アスパラギンカリウム",
      "ファムシクロビル",
      "アスパラギンカルシウム"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "ダントリウム",
    "correct": "ダントロレン",
    "choices": [
      "トラネキサム",
      "セフジニル",
      "ダントロレン",
      "ベザフィブラート"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "レスプレン",
    "correct": "エプラジノン",
    "choices": [
      "フルチカゾンフランカルボンエステル",
      "ゾニサミド",
      "スピロノラクトン",
      "エプラジノン"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "コートリル",
    "correct": "ヒドロコルチゾン",
    "choices": [
      "エンタカポン",
      "ニトログリセリン",
      "ヒドロコルチゾン",
      "ジラゼプ"
    ]
  }
]